theapptimes.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy - TheAppTimes

**Your privacy is important to us**

At  _TheAppTimes_ , (website address: https://theapptimes.com.) the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by our website and how it is used.

We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**What information do we collect?**

When you visit our website, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address via our newsletter. With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates. We may also use the information we collect from you to personalize your experience.

When you browse our website, we also automatically receive information in the log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, internet service provider (ISP), date/timestamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks. This data enables us to administer the site, analyze trends, track users’ movements around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such data is not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

When you leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Advertising cookies  **  
Google, our primary third-party advertising vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _TheAppTimes  _website. Google’s use of cookies enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to _TheAppTimes_ _.com_. Users may control the ads Google serves by visiting [Google’s ad settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Some of our other advertising partners, may use cookies on our site. (We also utilize affiliate links, and these affiliate vendors may use cookies as well.)

These third-party ad servers automatically receive your IP address from your web browser when you visit our site. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript and web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content you see.

These technologies collect information that is not personally identifiable (e.g., the pages you visit, which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our website.

These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

_TheAppTimes  _has no access to or control over cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

_TheAppTimes’  _privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**How do you get my consent?**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

When you provide us with personal information, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. You can do so by contacting us at editor@theapptimes.com.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so.

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**How we protect your data**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning.

**Changes to our Privacy**   **Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

**Contact Us**

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at editor@theapptimes.com.

Updated: 24-May-2018
